Go ahead,
>> Zach. U this morning, Mike Brown
announced that you and Duke will be
coming back for the next year. Uh and he
said that both of you are leaders that
this team needs moving forward. What
does it mean to you to have the owner
come out and say such positive things?
I'm appreciative of that, you know, and
um again, I think when when you're
you're aligned and you get together like
we get together and we're on the same
page, um I don't need those things said
about me, but but it's certainly helpful
as we move forward and provides clarity
and and so again, um appreciative of
that.
>> Did you need that? Did you
>> No, I didn't I didn't need that. I I
felt I've had plenty of conversations,
so um I didn't even
>> Why Why did you feel secure given how
the season went? I guess I more so I
don't need a I I didn't need a statement
but to I'll just continue my job and
>> um but I do appreciate him doing that
but um I I just feel like we are on a
path to really good things next year and
I think everybody that exit this
building today feels that. Players,
coaches, everybody involved with this
thing and that this season was a
disappointment. It didn't go the way we
wanted but
I'm already re-energized to get working
on 2026 and get back to work. doesn't
mean I won't take a couple days, but I
just feel like the the energy of this
group and the talent we have and the
progress a lot of these guys made that
we've got a chance to to be back in the
conversation of where we belong these
last couple years and have fallen short
of that. And so, um, I'm excitement and
I feel the excitement of all our players
and coaches to get back to that.
>> Given all the the meetings you've had
and discussions, what specifically do
you think needs to to happen to change
to get to that?
>> I think we have to just continue to
grow. You know, I think as speaking to
that, if if you look at just our season
this year, the last thing I left with
our our team is just the turnover
differential um where we lost games. We
weren't good enough on either side of
the ball and that was taking the ball
away from teams in the games we lost.
That was scoring points for the other
team on our offense, you know, and we
gave up nine touchdowns on our offense
this year. So, there's things as simple
as that. If you look at some of these
one-sore games where we just we didn't
do enough um just possessing the ball
and taking the ball away to win the game
and and it was as simple as that. That
doesn't mean that fundamentally that
doesn't mean that scheme will continue
to evolve and our players will continue
to grow. But just something as simple as
as the turnovers is a big key on why we
weren't as successful as we should.
>> Do you think you had enough talent on
the roster this year to win?
>> I do.
>> How do you how do you value evaluate
yourself as a head coach at the end of
every season? How do you go back and
look at whether you were successful or
not personally? I feel critical about
myself on decisions I made and ways I
can help other people and very open to
the feedback, you know, as we do the
exit interviews with the players and
sometimes part of it is how can I help
you be a better player. Um,
so always open to that. I I really feel
like I don't have an ego that way. I'm
open to criticism. I give myself
criticism. um hard on myself for
decisions you make in games, hard
decisions you made on personnel
decisions you made during the season,
all that kind of stuff. And and uh just
want to improve and be better and so
just continue to work on that.
>> What's the best thing you heard from a
player that they said to you?
>> That's a hard one. I I'd have to
process. You go through about 40
something of them today. So
>> I don't have that answer quite ready for
you.
>> About your exit interview with Joe.
>> What's that?
>> Your exit interview with
>> that'll be later this week. as you went
through why the season went the way it
did. Were there games, moments, trends
that really stuck with you um as you
were on that?
>> It's what game what game do you want to
talk about? It was it was a different
reason for every game it felt like and
that that that is frustrating. Um
because we got to be able to put our
finger on that and I just feel like we
we have the talent in this building
that's going to continue to grow. I
think if you look at our defense, you
look at all those guys that played
yesterday. Um, and I played these last
couple weeks, it's a bunch of young
talent, you know, first, second year,
third year guys with with a couple
veterans mixed in there, but all those
guys continue to grow and get better.
And the confidence they're going to have
going into next season, playing in the
scheme for second year, being around
these coaches for second year, being
around each other for second year. Um, I
think the chemistry on that side of the
ball was I mean, they've got a lot of
confidence right now coming out of these
last couple games. And so, I'm really
excited about that. offensively, you
know, we we've got everybody under
contract for the most part that um is a
big part of this thing and so I just
feel really strong that we'll have a
good off seasonason and and [snorts]
make a lot of waves going into the next
season.
>> Do you anticipate making any changes to
the staff?
>> I do not.
>> Over the years, when we ask players
about you, today included, they'll say
you're a player's coach. Why is that
your philosophy?
>> Well, I think that definition um I don't
always know what that definition means.
There's a part of this job where you've
got to make decisions that are hard
decisions that are not popular with
everybody on the team. But at the same
time, when guys have my respect and it's
decisions where I don't feel like it's
got to be my way or the highway, I want
the input on those from those guys. And
so I do like to open that up to players
um in ways that they can they can feel
ownership of this thing because I think
that's the best way to get the most out
of them and they enjoy walking in the
locker room every single day. They don't
dread walking in this building when they
feel like they've got ownership in what
we're doing schematically. Um how
they're going as a player, what we're
doing from a schedule standpoint. And
that's not to be said. I I make I make a
lot of those decisions myself because
you got to you got to make those
decisions. But, um, got a lot of guys
that I've been around for a long time as
players that I value their opinion and I
think they're going to help me make
educated decisions. And so, I think
maybe that's where some of it stems
from. I like to think I'm very honest
with these guys and and there's hard
conversations I've had with a lot of
these guys over the course of the season
that I think we both grew from. I think
those guys appreciate that. There may be
hard at the time for both of us, but um,
after the fact uh, we both grow from it
and our relationship becomes stronger
and maybe that's where part of that
stems from as well.
How much uh coach do you think the uh um
out coming in kind of a new scheme?
>> I [snorts] mean, how much of that do you
think that was a bigger impact
>> uh than you thought it was going to be?
Just the the time it took for me to get
[snorts] in the summer.
>> Yeah. No, I think I think we utilized a
lot of different people on that side of
the ball. I think you had a coaching
staff that came in and they worked
really hard this offseason this summer
to get together that really none of them
have worked together before. Um, so I
was really pleased with the growth of of
that side of the ball and I'm excited. I
mean, it's I'm excited about the
direction we're headed. And so I don't
think anybody's pleased with our record
this year and how it all ended, but um
that doesn't mean that there's not a lot
of excitement from our coaching staff
and our players going forward in the
future.
>> How can you better take advantage of
continuity? You've have a rare
continuity here and it hasn't paid off
as much in recent years. How can you
guys do a better job of taking advantage
of that? I think this will be, you know,
as as much continuity going in this
offseason as we've had. I think there's
um a role for all these guys that played
for us this year and and it doesn't mean
we won't add in free agency in the draft
to make ourselves better. Um but I'm
excited about a lot of these guys coming
back and and this being a bittersweet
feeling that's in our not a bittersweet
a bitter feeling um as we end the
season. And so um I'm just I'm excited
for the offseason. I'm excited to get
these guys back in April already.
They're probably sick of me right now,
but um I'm excited to get back to work
with these guys.
>> And that I mean how can you find better
use of continuity amongst decision?
>> This is a really tough question
>> and amongst decision makers like how can
you with between Duke I mean you guys
are back working together and how can
you guys do a better job
>> of utilizing the fact that you've worked
together so much this offseason when it
hasn't paid off as much at least.
>> I think it's going to help. We've had
this whole staff here together now going
into our second year talking about the
defense guys. So that helps as we talk
about personnel, as we're with the
scouts, as we're with Duke. Everyone's
got a better feel for each other. The
coaches have been here now for two years
on the defensive side of the ball, new
align coach. So, everyone's got a better
feel for our play style, what we're
trying to do. And so, I think that
really will give us a lot of momentum
going into the offseason of, okay,
here's how we're going to utilize guys.
Here's here's what we need to make
oursel as good as possible. Um, here's
some things we can improve on on the
offensive side of the ball as well. So I
I I really have a lot of confidence in
the relationship we have amongst the
coaches and the scouts to to make sure
that we fulfill our full potential.
>> When I think of when you guys went on
the run in 21 and 22, I think of a lot
of guys that you added externally, the
DJs, the the Trey,
>> how important is it to have
an active and and productive free agency
period this offseason for you?
>> Well, I think every year is going to be
a little different in terms of that. Um,
I'm excited to jump into that period to
see see where we can help ourselves, see
what roles we need to fill. Those are
conversations that we'll have over the
next couple weeks. You know, it's it's
still day after the season, so we're not
there yet. But I am excited to to
approach that process. I know our
scouting department is excited, too, and
we'll see where it ends up. But, um,
there's a lot of clarity, I think, on on
in all phases of it of where we can head
and where we can improve upon and and
we'll get after that.
>> So, I follow up on that. It's pretty
well documented how involved [snorts]
you are on the offensive side of the
ball. Do you plan to be more involved in
terms of the acquisition part of getting
more defensive help this off season
based off kind of what's happened on the
defensive side of the ball the last few
years?
>> I think my role is always very similar
in that. It's not just on the offensive
side of the ball. Obviously, um, our
defense coaches have their lifetime
backgrounds on the defensive side. So, I
get my opinion on how it affects the
offense and how I think it'll affect the
team and the intangible stuff that I
think can really help us. Um, but I also
got a lot of people we trust to help
with those decisions as well. And that's
no different than offense. I lean on
those offense guys as well because they
put in the work at their position. Um,
they know what we're looking for. So, I
I think it all it all works together.
You you took a lot of pride, Zach, in
the first couple of years building a
culture, uh, building a locker room that
was selfaccountable, if that's even a
word to use, but
>> players who held themselves accountable,
held each other accountable. Are you
going to reassess that process this off
season? Like, who's holding each other
accountable?
>> No, I think I I think that's always
evolving. I think every year you're
going to have guys come and go, and so
I'm never going to put it on a guy
that's not ready for it. I think a lot
of it um guys take that upon themselves.
They realized the moment they can they
can really come up and start doing that.
To give an example, I think Sam Huard
grew into that role over time. You know,
he felt more comfortable with it because
he'd proven himself on the field. So
then he felt like he could start
speaking more. There's been guys we
brought in that have immediately felt
that role because maybe they're more
veteran. They've been with another
program and they earn that somewhere
else you bring in. There's a lot of
different ways where this thing could
take shape and I think we're open to all
possibilities of leaders being here and
growing, leaders coming in and and help
hoping they helping the accountability
be the be the best they can be.
>> What what piece of the pie to use the
phrase, what piece of the pie is good
solid leadership when you're evaluating
a free agent or bringing somebody else?
>> It's part of it. You know, there there's
times when you feel like you have enough
of it where maybe you're just taking
more of a talent. Um, but I think it's
always helpful if if you got a lot of
guys that have that intangible quality
to where they can help those around them
be better players. Not just the talent
themselves, but the guys lined up next
to them, they're going to elevate their
level of play for whatever reason, their
leadership, their football IQ, um, their
communication skills. As many of those
guys you can add that are force
multipliers for other positions, you
always are open to it.
>> Had to play a lot of rookies this year.
Did you guys do you feel like you guys
added enough veteran free agents last
offseason?
>> Yeah, I I think we we made the decisions
that were best for us at the time and
we'll always look at that process this
offseason and see what fits us going
into 2026, but um we were all on the
same page with everything we were doing
in the offseason and and uh I don't
expect anything different this year.
>> Like you said, there there always
different paths you can take in an off
season. tangibly. What is the process
like sitting down especially with the
defensive side of the ball with Duke
with the coaching staff and figuring all
right this is what you're going to
>> Yeah I think different than last year
when was Al's last game January
something in the national championship
and then we hired the staff you know
after interviewed him after the
championship got the staff that was
probably J February when we were getting
all that thing put together and then
you're talking about okay what's our
scheme look like a bunch of guys that
were coming together and then okay we
got to look at these draft picks and
these free agents as well. So now you
got a much cleaner operation where we
got a chance. Okay, we've coached these
guys that are here and so where can we
get better? And so that that process is
going to happen so much sooner and where
we get with the scouting department and
we make all the decisions we got to make
on on improving our team and um
schematically and personnel wise and and
so I I feel uh I'm excited for that
process to start because it's going to
be so much sooner than it was last year.
And if you know if you want to go ahead
and say exactly what you're going to do
this offseason, that'd be great. But
>> yeah, I'm not going to do that.
>> Do you do you know exactly how you want
it to look or is that something you're
going to flesh out through these
conversations?
>> Both. I I think got a good idea of where
we can help ourselves in all areas. Like
I said, scheme, personnel. Um, and it'll
evolve as you have conversations and you
hear different people's opinions and
feedback and you iron that out. I don't
want a lot of agreements. I want
disagreements on on who fits us and how
to utilize a guy and I think that's all
healthy dialogue to improve ourselves
and so um that'll be a part of the
process that we go through.
>> How do you square it sounds like you
want to you know keep a lot of the same
things intact moving forward next year.
How do you square that with Joe and
Jamar being so vocal about something
obviously needing to change as you all
need to figure out how to get back to
being a a playoff team again?
>> I I feel like I'm on the same page with
those guys.
>> But what what have you identified what
what possibly could be different? like
what would you ideally like for this
thing to look next year?
>> Yeah, I I've got a sense of it. I'm not
gonna broadcast it all today, but I I've
got a sense of how we can help ourselves
going forward. You
>> have what they think needs to change.
Have they voiced that to you yet, or is
that something that you hope to
>> Like I said, I'll I'll follow through
with Joe later on. I met with Jamar and
a lot of other guys today. So, um I've
got a good feel for where most of us
stand.
>> Every offensive starter, but one is
under contract. Do you feel like you're
in a unique position where you really
only have to address one side of the
ball?
>> I mean, that's the truth of it, you
know, and and so there's no real sugar
coating that. You got a bunch of guys
coming back and um it's exciting because
you can focus your energy and
there's so many guys on that side of the
ball that really their growth was
accelerated over the last half of the
year that you're really excited about
their future here as starters, as role
players. Um, so I feel like we're in a
tremendous position going into this
offseason where um, our expectations are
going to be sky-high and we're going to
work like heck to meet those
expectations, but I think the players
and coaches all see the direction we're
headed and and so there's a lot of
positive energy heading into the
offseason.
>> You were asked about culture, Zach, a
little bit earlier and over seven years,
I'm sure that evolves and what culture
is and how it can help you win games. as
you now have that banked into your head
of what can help, how do you see the
vision of what you want your culture to
be as you go towards year eight?
>> I think from talking to players, there's
been so much um team bonding, all the
off the- field stuff that's happened
this year that's going to continue to
grow. guys on both sides of the ball um
sharing and all that stuff to where I'm
encouraged as I've ever been in terms of
how our team fits together and and just
not just in the football meeting room
and on practice, but all the stuff off
the field that guys have done a greatly
good job growing that part of our team
and and hope that continues to grow. You
know, we don't just that's not just a
one-year thing and then you you put on
the back burner and let's focus on
something else next year. Um, I've
always challenged these guys to be a
very close team, be the closest team in
the NFL, and I think they've really
taken that to heart. Guys brought that
up today in my meeting. You just watch
our team play these these last three
games. I know yesterday was yesterday.
It was just we should not have lost that
game, but we did. Um, but that wasn't
due to lack of energy and and guys doing
a great job over these last couple weeks
and focusing on it and giving ourselves
a chance to win.
>> How valuable would it be to bring back
Joe Flacco?
>> I think it'd be valuable. I I think um
he's a starting quarterback in the NFL
and [snorts] so I think anytime
you've experienced that and you're able
to get him back, that'd be great. Now,
I'll let him speak for himself. So, he
he'll have to look at those
opportunities, but I know that he
enjoyed his time here. I think it was
good for all of us to to get a chance to
know each other and and we'll see what
his future holds for him. He's got to
make that decision. He's earned that as
an old man. He's earned the right to to
decide what he wants to do. [laughter]
Uh but I do know he wants to keep
playing, you know, and I appreciate that
about him.
Um, so again, what what a what a fun
time that was getting here, getting
getting to know him and and the effect
he had on our team and um and we'll just
see how it shakes out in the future.
>> It sounds like you're hoping he's back
whether or not.
>> I would hope that he's back. Yeah, I
would. But but again, I I also respect
him at the same time that he's got to
make decisions for himself.
>> I know that you're pleased with what
you've seen from the defensive side of
the ball since the buy, but when you
look at holistically this season, and I
know you're not going to share exactly
what your plan is. I'm asking this more
of like how you would explain to the
fans like what they can expect and why
they should expect the defense to be
better next year. What do you feel like
you were missing most holistically on
defense this year?
>> Well, I mean, I think you you missed for
most of the season your highest played
player on offense and defense, you know,
and that that hurt us, especially key
parts of the year early on. Um, so that
that's a challenge and and we overcame
that over time, you know. I think all
the guys grew because of that. more guys
got opportunity and their reps increased
and and and I saw growth in their game
that really helped us. So for me, you
look at defensively some missed tackles,
some missed opportunities early on and
then those guys kept playing, you know,
young players kept playing. They kept
improving over and over and the game
slowed down for them and their
communication sped up and their ability
to make plays on the balls and create
turnovers sped up. So you saw that
evolution over time and that's what's
encouraging to me is I saw the growth in
that entire unit and seeing
[clears throat] the trajectory that
they're on and and I've got high
expectations for that group moving
forward.
>> As you go through roster construction
this offseason, what's the biggest
lesson you take from last offseason?
>> I I don't know that there's a specific
thing I'd give you that's that's a great
answer here. I think every every
offseason is a little bit new. Um for
example, just just the staff being here
and we're done. The scheme, we got it.
We'll make our tweaks. We got plenty of
time, but we all know it. So now we get
more time to focus on helping the
scouting department with just our
opinions on the guys and our evaluations
on guys and how it fits. So just to that
extent, I mean, you just look at the
offseasons over time here. You're
talking about COVID, you're talking
about the second year of COVID when
you're not in the building as much and
all the different things that have
happened. Staff changed last year. It's
rare that you have the same offseason
two years in a row. And so I feel like
we're in a better place this offseason
with our staff and with the players we
have coming back um to make really good
decisions to help our team moving
forward.
>> From a player standpoint,
>> from a player standpoint on defense,
what's the biggest piece that you think
you already have position? Well, I think
at I think at every position, you've got
guys that are showed me a lot of growth
and potential and so however you add
around that to to supplement that um is
a really positive thing for that unit.
So, I I just think if you go position by
position and you look at the veterans
that have helped us and the young guys
that are continuing to send, there's a
lot to be excited about.
the last really since 22 and free for
agency there have been a lot of very
good players who have signed here saying
like I can win a ring here and that
that's part of the pitch and that's
something they value and believe in. Do
you feel like because you have Joe Jamar
and T that pitch still works?
>> I do. I do. I think you know when you
get a chance to we don't meet with the
free agents necessarily because it's
it's a wacky process that way. Um, but I
think people know and there's respect
there for for our team and how we
operate and um, for guys that talk to
our players in the building, I hate to
speak for them, but I think that they
really like it here and they like how we
operate and how we treat them and all
that kind of stuff. And so they see the
opportunity here. here. And so I think
just through word of mouth over the last
several years, the feedback I've always
gotten gotten is really good that that
guys kind of see the opportunity here
and what it's like and hear from their
friends that have signed here and and
had a really good experience. And so um
I trust that process.
>> How much does this organization value
guard the guard position?
>> Um how that that's a hard one to answer.
I mean, we value good players that help
us win. And so, um, I can't put a a
metric on how you value it, but I was
really excited this year about the
growth of Dylan. I thought he did a
really nice job. I thought Dalton did a
great job at red guard for us. I'm
excited for the future of Jaylen Rivers
as well. Um, so again, I I think I was
excited about the direction that that
room headed this year and I know Dalton
signed a contract and we'll we'll work
through that and make our best decisions
for a team, but um I I can't put a
metric on how you value guard.
>> Given what Dalton brought, is it almost
surprising that he's bounced around the
way he has after getting here and
fighting at home? I mean, he's
>> Yeah, I I don't know the reason for all
that. You know, it's I I've enjoyed my
experience with him. I I think he he did
a great job for us. I loved his presence
in the locker room. I loved his presence
in the O line room. I liked my
interactions with him. He's he's helped
me. I think he's non nonsense, straight
to the point. I appreciate that about
him. Um he's a big eight guy at heart
and so I think that's where that stems
from, you know, amid a guy from that
region. So I can appreciate that.
>> Zack with [snorts]
uh Al having a little bit of a shorter
runway into the job. I think you spoke
about that a little bit in different
words just because of the title, the run
to the championship game with Notre
Dame. Um, just wondering from from that
point forward when you got the defensive
coaching staff set up and now that you
can look back through the full body of
work of the 17 games,
>> how did you see him grow into that role
as
>> I I just I think you know as that that
staff really worked hard to come
together and get on the same page with
scheme and and how we're going to coach
these guys and um so like anything I I
saw great growth from that side of the
ball and and you know post by those guys
gave up, you know, 18 point something
points a game, you know, over the last
eight games. And and there's a lot of
statistics I can read where it shows
market improvement. Um, and so again, I
I'm just I like the direction that that
group is headed. I like the direction
our team is headed. Um, I don't say that
I know how it sounds when we come off
the record we just had, but but again, I
I've got a lot of excitement and I'm
excited to get back to work and get
these guys ready for next year. As
someone who's gone through a lot of
seven offseasons now with Duke, can you
shed some light on why you think Duke
Tobin is so good to partner with you in
creating this roster the way that you
guys need?
>> I think he's got no ego. Um he's not in
it for himself. He's in it to make the
Bengals the best we can be. And there's
no ulterior motive there. And he loves
his place. He's been here a long time.
There's nothing more than Duke wants
than to win a Super Bowl and and provide
a roster that matches that expectation.
And so, um, it's easy for me to work
with him. It's easy for me to work with
the staff. They're good people. They're
around, so you get a chance to really
know them and grow with them. We've all
grown together. I mean, that whole
department, our coaching staff has grown
together. Um, and just the the easiest
thing I can say is about Duke is there's
no ego. He just he just wants what's
best for the team. And so, there's
nothing nothing other than that. And so,
um, I enjoy working with him every day.
We got a great relationship and I'm
confident that we're on the same page
and we'll make this thing the best it
can be.
>> This is probably the greatest sense of
what are conversations like with with
Duke when you have a season like this
during it.
>> I mean, we have so many conversations,
you know, so we're both frustrated. I
mean, it's um we didn't meet
expectations and so that that's
frustrating for both of us and um we
certainly share that with each other and
how we can grow and and what we both
think are are reasons we can grow and
things that we've got to be better at.
And I think when you've got two
like-minded people, you can work through
all that stuff and get on the same page.
>> Given the statement from Mike today and
kind of the lack of postseason success
you've had, how do you gauge a sense of
urgency going into this offseason
compared to maybe other offseasons where
you've had success?
>> You're going to get my best every day
whether whether we're coming off of
Super Bowl appearance or the season we
just had, you know? And so,
um, I think our urgency is is always a
word that we would utilize because
that's just I feel like it's our DNA.
We're not lacadasical. we're not going
to take time off when we should be
grinding and getting stuff done. Um, so
I I think that my feeling doesn't
change. I'm appreciative I have this
opportunity. I I know how grateful I am
to be sitting here and have another
opportunity to go make a run and win a
division and go back to the playoffs and
do all those things that we love to do.
That's why we do this. To elevate a city
and a fan base and make their year like
there's I don't take that for granted
and I know what we've how we've left
them feeling the last couple years. And
so, um, there's nothing more that
creates more urgency than for us to go
win for ourselves because of the work we
put in, win for our families that have
supported us, and win for the city that
has supported us through thick and thin.
Um, and I know what it felt like in 2021
and 2022. And we we have got to get back
to that as quickly as possible so that
we can all enjoy this ride. And and
that's what we're going to do.
>> Do you feel like you got to win folks
back?
>> Um, I don't worry about that. I I know
winning makes believers of us all. I
that makes sense. I can understand how
that quote came to be because that's a
true statement. It's written in our
building. We see it every day. Um but
that's the truth. You know, you go
through hard times and there's
disappointment and then all of a sudden
you win some games, you're right back in
the thick and people can't wait to jump
on board. So, um I love the P. It's it's
it is great being here and having
passionate fans. It it is. And um I
don't take that for granted. There's
other places you go where doesn't seem
it seems like they're indifferent maybe
is they're sitting in the stadium and
the game's going on and here you know
they're not indifferent here they're
passionate and they have high
expectations and they want us to win and
they're going to support us and they
really want to support a winner and so
we got to give them that and and we're
going to work our tails off to do that
for them.
>> Zach, there was so much talk last year
about how this team can get off to a
fast start because that seemed to be
buzz theme for the last
>> What do you got for me next year?
[laughter]
about next year. What are you going to
think about this off season in in that
similar regard
>> about what you could change that may may
have been different?
>> Well, we talked about starting fast. I I
I really think closing out games and
finishing and however that looks like
finishing the game on offense by
possessing the ball and finishing with
points and ending the game or defense
getting off the field on a two-minute
drill. Um special teams making a play
that changes the game and leading the
game. So, you got to be creative with
that thinking, you know, over the course
of the offseason and training camp. Um,
but it's certainly on my mind, you know,
as you look at some of these games and
and I think the games we lost were were
all its own story. Every game wasn't
necessarily the same thing, the same
reason. Everybody had their hand in it
in all three phases. Um, but that's the
part that I'm I'm excited to explore is
how can we change, you know, kind of how
about go go go about things in training
camp, the offseason to um tighten that
up because there we didn't finish well
enough in a lot of these games.
>> You had a burrow deal to get done two
years ago. T Jamar and Trey this past
offseason. There's really nothing like
that this offseason. How does that
affect team building this off season?
Well, that's um I don't have a great
answer for you there because there's
still guys that that have earned the
right to have those conversations and
and I'll let Duke and all them have
those conversations. Um
so that it's kind of the best I can give
you. Um I think it's it is good to have
a lot of guys under contract coming back
that are ready for new opportunity and
the next opportunity and so we'll
continue to focus on those guys.
>> Is there a path for Trey to return?
>> Trey Henderson.
>> Trey Hendrickson. There's always a path.
>> One more thing, uh, Zach, you had
mentioned, I think you expect no changes
on your coaching process,
>> correct?
>> Uh, does that also mean, uh, likely no
interviews with any other teams?
>> I can't answer that. That's too early in
the process to see. Yeah.
>> Okay. Thank you. Inverter.